[{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974916223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":12302,"timeElapsed":64854},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974924382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8157,"timeElapsed":73013},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974929451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":5067,"timeElapsed":78082},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974935916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6464,"timeElapsed":84547},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974941677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5759,"timeElapsed":90308},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974944107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2429,"timeElapsed":92738},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974947017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2908,"timeElapsed":95648},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974952237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5218,"timeElapsed":100868},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974955612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3374,"timeElapsed":104243},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974967867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":10920,"timeElapsed":116498},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974969907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2038,"timeElapsed":118538},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974971691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1783,"timeElapsed":120322},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974974512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2820,"timeElapsed":123143},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974978667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4154,"timeElapsed":127298},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974986752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":8083,"timeElapsed":135383},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974989451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2698,"timeElapsed":138082},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974993321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3869,"timeElapsed":141952},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734974995287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":1964,"timeElapsed":143917},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975001901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5593,"timeElapsed":150532},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975003267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1364,"timeElapsed":151898},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975004497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1229,"timeElapsed":153128},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975005802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1304,"timeElapsed":154433},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975008322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":156952},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975010302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1979,"timeElapsed":158933},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975012042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":160673},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975013842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1798,"timeElapsed":162473},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975015087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1244,"timeElapsed":163718},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975020937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4874,"timeElapsed":169568},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975022377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1439,"timeElapsed":171008},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975023787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":1409,"timeElapsed":172418},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975025226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1438,"timeElapsed":173857},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975027837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2610,"timeElapsed":176468},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975029441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1603,"timeElapsed":178072},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975031151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1709,"timeElapsed":179782},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975032577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1424,"timeElapsed":181208},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975034031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1453,"timeElapsed":182662},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975042731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":7453,"timeElapsed":191362},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975044082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1350,"timeElapsed":192713},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975045417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1333,"timeElapsed":194047},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975046722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1304,"timeElapsed":195353},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975048299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1575,"timeElapsed":196930},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975049885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1586,"timeElapsed":198516},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975052077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2190,"timeElapsed":200708},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975053562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1484,"timeElapsed":202193},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975055077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":1513,"timeElapsed":203708},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975061872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5923,"timeElapsed":210503},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975063326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1453,"timeElapsed":211957},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975064961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":1634,"timeElapsed":213592},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975066641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":1679,"timeElapsed":215272},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975071337,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4695,"timeElapsed":219968},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975074516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3178,"timeElapsed":223147},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975076497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1980,"timeElapsed":225128},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975078146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1648,"timeElapsed":226777},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975079915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":1768,"timeElapsed":228546},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975081942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2025,"timeElapsed":230573},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975086562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3748,"timeElapsed":235193},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975088167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1604,"timeElapsed":236798},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975089456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1288,"timeElapsed":238087},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975090837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1379,"timeElapsed":239467},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975092337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1499,"timeElapsed":240968},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975094241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1903,"timeElapsed":242872},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975096044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1802,"timeElapsed":244675},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975097617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1571,"timeElapsed":246248},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975099236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1618,"timeElapsed":247867},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975103616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3449,"timeElapsed":252247},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975104982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":1364,"timeElapsed":253613},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975106256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":1273,"timeElapsed":254887},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975107712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":1454,"timeElapsed":256343},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975110127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2414,"timeElapsed":258758},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975111806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":1678,"timeElapsed":260437},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975113336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":1529,"timeElapsed":261967},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975114867,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":1529,"timeElapsed":263498},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975116291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":1423,"timeElapsed":264922},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975124256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":6899,"timeElapsed":272887},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975125906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1648,"timeElapsed":274537},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975127541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1633,"timeElapsed":276172},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975129086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1544,"timeElapsed":277717},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975130946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":1859,"timeElapsed":279577},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975132582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":1634,"timeElapsed":281213},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975134216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":1633,"timeElapsed":282847},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975137861,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3644,"timeElapsed":286491},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975139932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2070,"timeElapsed":288563},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975141581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":1648,"timeElapsed":290212},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975149441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6913,"timeElapsed":298072},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975151197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1754,"timeElapsed":299827},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975152351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1153,"timeElapsed":300982},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975153598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1246,"timeElapsed":302229},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975155141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1542,"timeElapsed":303772},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975157330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2188,"timeElapsed":305961},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975159386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2054,"timeElapsed":308017},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975160991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1604,"timeElapsed":309622},{"subjectID":"7qomycyj8r","prolificID":"67462fa506e005a3bcdfe67f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d77ec12422b88ef1e46","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975162297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1304,"timeElapsed":310927}]